Preliminary Inventory to the Servas International records
Hoover Institution Archives
Servas International records
1946-2010
2010C15
Hoover Institution Archives
107 manuscript boxes, 3 oversize boxes (44.0 linear feet)
Bylaws, minutes, manuals, bulletins, newsletters, correspondence, writings, notes, reports, traveler and host lists and files, financial records, printed matter, and audiovisual material relating to promotion of peace and international understanding, and especially to sponsorship of international travelers and international hospitality. Includes records of United States Servas, the American branch of Servas International, and papers of Bob Liutweiler, founder of Servas International.
Servas International.
Liutweiler, Bob, 1918-2008.
United States Servas.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items, computer media, and digital files. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos, films, or digital files during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2010.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Historical Note
Servas (meaning "we serve" in Esperanto) is a cultural exchange organization that was first established in 1948 by a group of individuals who hailed from a number of peace organizations in England and the United States. Its mission is to promote diversity and cultural understanding through work, study, and a travel exchange program.
Among its founding members was peace activist Preston Bob Liutweiler, an American who held a strong belief in peace-building and an opposition to World War II and the draft. Luitweiler’s and the other founding members’ convictions on social justice and culture exchange led them to create the Servas program.
The founders hoped that through their travel exchange program, which is based on hospitality and an "open door" travel policy, they would be able to promote an intercultural effort for social justice and compassion. As a result, a global network of hosts was established so that people from all over the world have a chance to visit each other in their homes and learn from each other’s cultural philosophies and experiences.
The program is represented by hosts in over 135 nations. Its members come from various educational, religious, and social backgrounds.
Source: "US Servas." US Servas. January 1, 2010. Accessed December 4, 2014. https://www.usservas.org/.
Scope and Content of Collection
Materials in this collection document the mission and peace building efforts of the Servas International organization through: articles, brochures, bulletins, clippings, conference materials, correspondence, digital media, handbooks, manuals, meeting minutes, newsletters, notes, photographs, publications, reports, scrapbooks, and writings.
When available, the original folder titles have been retained. An index to major groups has been created and included in this inventory; researchers should note, however, that the index is not exhaustive and not all the materials in the collection fall within the groups listed.
Individuals with interest in international travel exchange programs, social justice, and peace building should find this collection of particular interest.
Index of Major Groups
An index of major groups has been created to draw attention to common groups of materials and their physical location within the collection. Major groups of this collection are: Administrative File, Bob Liutweiler File, Conference File, Digital Media File, Financial Records File, Geographical File, Organizational History File, Photographs File, Printed Matter File, and Travelers and Hosts File.
10, 11, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 28, 22, 29, 30, 31, 32, 40, 42, 43, 44, 45, 53, 55, 61, 62, 63, 65, 66, 69, 70, 74, 76, 77, 78, 79, 80, 82, 88, 89, 90, 91, 92, 93, 94, 95, 96, 99, 101, 102, 103, 105, 106, 107, 108, 109, 110 Administrative File, 1946-2010:
Consists of correspondence, meeting minutes, projects, office and annual reports, office manuals and handbooks, staffing task force documents, cooperative endeavors with various peace and social justice organizations, government and legal filings, and client papers.
19, 26-28, 38, 41, 45, 71, 72, 78, 79, 80 Bob Liutweiler File, 1949-2008:
Consists of files pertaining to the life and work of Bob Liutweiler: writings and stories, research materials and subject files, correspondence, notebooks with writing ideas, family documents and photos, as well as documents on various projects Liutweiler was involved in, such as the sustainable gardening project.
4, 9, 11, 12, 14, 16, 17, 18, 29, 39, 61, 67, 68, 69, 88, 89, 90, 92, 94, 95, 97, 98, 99, 107, 108, 110
Conference File, 1966-2008:
Consists of national and international conference and retreat materials, brochures, conference workshop materials, and attendance sheets. Includes minutes from various conferences: Los Angeles-1976, Denmark-1978, India-1980, Israel-1983, Rome-1986, France-1992, Melbourne-1995, Antigua and Guatemala-1998, Mexico-2006, and Thailand-2007.
4, 8, 10, 29, 31, 37, 61, 75, 78, 81, 97, 100, 108
Digital Media File, circa 1990-2006:
Comprised of zip disks, DDS-3 tapes, analog videotape, mini and compact cassette tapes, CDs, floppy disks, and a hard drive.
12, 16, 17, 18, 19, 21, 23, 25, 29, 48, 50, 74, 87, 88, 91, 92, 95
Financial Records File, 1962-2007:
Consists of application for tax exemptions, annual reports, donation and contributor documents, orders for Servas buttons, financial mismanagement materials, expenses and balance books, invoices and tax records, Financial Committee minutes, treasurer files, and financial statements.
15, 41, 80, 90, 91
Geographical File, 1973-2006:
Comprised of correspondence, newsletters, and financial records regarding various geographical areas: Africa, Asia, Australia, Canada, Caribbean and Central America, China, USSR, and Europe.
7, 8, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 21, 38, 42, 43, 69, 93, 97, 99
Organizational History File, 1952-2004:
Consists of correspondence, articles, memorabilia, various documents pertaining to the history and background of the Servas organization.
1, 6, 29, 30, 35-36, 38, 45, 76, 85, 100
Photographs File, 1950-2001:
Contains photographs, negatives, slides, contact sheets, albums, and scrapbooks documenting various Servas events, activities, meetings, and trips.
1, 5, 9, 11, 12, 13, 14, 16, 18, 19, 28, 29, 38, 40, 41, 43, 66, 69, 71, 72, 73, 76, 78, 79, 81, 83, 88, 89, 92, 95, 97, 98, 99, 102, 110
Printed Matter File, 1952-2008:
Includes articles, clippings, publications, pamphlets, brochures, postcards, newsletters, handbooks, bulletins, flyers, posters, and publicity materials.
2, 3, 4, 11, 12, 13, 14, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20, 21, 29, 30, 31, 41, 42, 46, 51, 53, 54, 55, 56, 57, 58, 59, 60, 68, 73, 74, 75, 76, 78, 79, 83, 84, 89, 90, 91, 95, 98, 99, 103-106, 109, 110
Travelers and Hosts File, 1969-2010:
Includes various materials pertaining to the travel of Servas members: key persons files, correspondence and information sheets, documentation on group trips, information on international coordinators, host lists, host renewal forms, traveler renewal cards, information on travel fees, interviewer handbooks, host list supplements, information on the travel program, surveys, host welcome packets, interviewer checklists that were submitted with the travelers applications, alphabetical travelers files, and traveler reports.
Peace.; International travel.; United States--Relations.
- Miscellaneous pamphlets on agriculture in Mexico, 1986 (Box 1)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Photo album of Servas events and activities, 1991 (Box 1)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Photographs, negatives, and contact sheets, 1978-2001 (Box 1)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Key person correspondence and information sheets, A-D, 1987-2007 (Box-folder 2: 1-27)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Key person correspondence and information sheets, E-M, 1987-2007 (Box-folder 3: 1-36)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Key person correspondence and information sheets, M-P, 1987-2007 (Box-folder 4: 1-15)
- United States Servas, Inc. - 7 zip disks, undated (Box 4)
- United States Servas, Inc. - VHS videocassettes. Servas conference, Thailand, 2007 (Box 4)
- United States Servas, Inc. - VHS videocassettes. Servas Los Angeles, 1976 (Box 4)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Card files, miscellaneous, undated (Box 5)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Photographs, 1976-2001 (Box 6)
- Organizational history, 1978-1998 (Box-folder 7: 1-3)
  Scope and Contents note
  Includes conference materials, newsletters, and pamphlets.
- Organizational history and newsletters from Servas International General Assemblies, 1984-2004 (Box-folder 8: 1-5)
  Includes Spain, Peru, the Netherlands, Canada, France, Australia, Switzerland, and others.
- Antonie Fried file, 1985-1999 (Box-folder 8: 6)
- Compact disc. "Servas International Archives and data on Bob [Liutweiler's] hard drive,", undated (Box-folder 8: 7)
- Servas International News, newsletters, 1974-1998 (Box-folder 9: 1-3)
- Servas International News, newsletters, 1999-2004 (Box-folder 9: 4)
  Includes newsletters from Servas Great Britain and Israel.
- Servas International Conference, Antigua, Guatemala, 1998 April (Box-folder 9: 5)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Board of Directors file, 1992 (Box-folder 10: 1)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Board of Directors file, 1996 (Box-folder 10: 2)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Board of Directors file, 1997 (Box-folder 10: 3)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Board of Directors file, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 10: 4)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Compact disc. "Servas trip to Iceland and Europe, 2003 September-October. Bob Neuhauser and Dorothy Killehreur" (Box-folder 10: 5)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Newsletter and activities, 2005 (Box-folder 11: 1)
- Servas International. Conferences, 2001, 2004, 2006 (Box-folder 11: 2)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Group trips, 1974-1982 (Box-folder 11: 3)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Board minutes, 1974-1992 (Box-folder 11: 4)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Bylaws, 1989 (Box-folder 11: 5)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Brochures and handbook, 1978-1999 (Box-folder 11: 6)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Alternatives to Servas, 1984-1992 (Box-folder 11: 7)
- Servas International. Key lists (contact lists), 1969-2005 (Box-folder 12: 1)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Financial records. Application for tax exemption, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 12: 2)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Peace and Social Justice Committee minutes and related materials, 1980-1991 (Box-folder 12: 3)
- United States Servas, Inc. - U.S. Peace Secretary newsletters, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 12: 4)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Lists of key people, U.S., 1977-1993 (Box-folder 12: 5)
- United States Servas, Inc. - U.S. national conferences, 1971-1989 (Box-folder 12: 6)
- U.S. Servas News, newsletters, 1954-1972 (Box-folder 13: 1)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Information sent to key people, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 13: 2)
- U.S. Servas history and background, 1963-1975 (Box-folder 13: 3)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Programs involving disabled, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 13: 4)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Handbooks, 1986 (Box-folder 13: 5)
- Handbooks, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 13: 6)
- History, 1952-1988 (Box-folder 13: 7)
- Publicity, 1976-1987 (Box-folder 13: 8)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Information for hosts and travellers, 1977-1988 (Box-folder 14: 1)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Working committees and volunteers, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 14: 2)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Reminiscences, 1999 (Box-folder 14: 3)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Publicity, 1984-1987 (Box-folder 14: 4)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Travel fees, 1987 (Box-folder 14: 5)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Special events, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 14: 6)
- United States Servas, Inc. - NAFSA members, international programs, 2003 (Box-folder 14: 7)
- U.S. Servas interviewer handbook, 2001 (Box-folder 14: 8)
- Geographical files
  Includes correspondence, newsletters, and financial records.
  - Africa, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - Africa, South, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 15: 2)
  - Asia, East, 1986 (Box-folder 15: 3)
  - Australia, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 15: 4)
  - Bolivia, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 15: 5)
  - Britain, 1986 (Box-folder 15: 6)
  - Canada, 1973 (Box-folder 15: 7)
  - Caribbean and Central America, 1980 (Box-folder 15: 8)
  - China, USSR, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 15: 9)
  - Denmark, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 15: 10)
  - Europe, general, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 15: 11)
  - Europe, Eastern, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 15: 12-13)
  - France, circa 1980 (Box-folder 15: 14)
  - Germany, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 15: 15)
  - Holland, 1977-1991 (Box-folder 15: 16)
  - India, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 15: 17)
  - Ireland, 1987 (Box-folder 15: 18)
  - Israel, 1988 (Box-folder 15: 19)
  - Japan, 1988 (Box-folder 15: 20)
  - Mexico, 1991 (Box-folder 15: 21)
  - Near East, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 15: 22)
  - Norway and Sweden, 1971-1977 (Box-folder 15: 23)
  - Russia, 1990 (Box-folder 15: 24)
  - United States, 1987 (Box-folder 15: 25)
- Correspondence of Reva King, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 15: 26)
- Lists of involved people, 1972-1991 (Box-folder 16: 1)
- Peace secretaries of member countries, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 16: 2)
- Finances, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 16: 3)
- Reports on Servas representatives at the United Nations, 1984-1989 (Box-folder 16: 4)
- Allied organizations, 1983 (Box-folder 16: 5)
- Newsletters, 1976-1991 (Box-folder 16: 6)
- Conferences, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 16: 7)
- United States Servas, Inc. - International coordinators, undated (Box-folder 17: 1)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Office correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 17: 2)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Calendar of events, undated (Box-folder 17: 3)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Logos, 1996 (Box-folder 17: 4)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Tax exemption, 1977 (Box-folder 17: 5)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Financial records (annual reports), 1976-1977 (Box-folder 17: 6)
- United States Servas, Inc. - U.S. National Conferences brochures, 1999-2005 (Box-folder 17: 7)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Meeting sign-in sheets, 2006 (Box-folder 17: 8)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Time chart, undated (Box-folder 17: 9)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Letter of invitation, undated (Box-folder 17: 10)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Donations, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 17: 11)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Host reports, 2006 (Box-folder 17: 12-14)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Key note ideas and comments, 2000 (Box-folder 18: 1)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Outreach activities, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 18: 2-3)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Brochures, circa 1990
  - Brazil (Box-folder 18: 4)
  - Canada (Box-folder 18: 5)
  - Central American (Box-folder 18: 6)
  - French (Box-folder 18: 7)
  - German (Box-folder 18: 8)
  - Italian (Box-folder 18: 9)
  - Portuguese (Box-folder 18: 10)
  - Russia (Box-folder 18: 11)
  - Spanish (Box-folder 18: 12)
- United States Servas, Inc. - International handbook, 1991 (Box-folder 18: 13)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Letter of invitation, undated (Box-folder 18: 14)
- United States Servas, Inc. - International forms, undated (Box-folder 18: 15)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Miscellaneous office files, undated (Box-folder 18: 16-19)
- United States Servas, Inc. - History, undated (Box-folder 18: 20)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Camp counselors flyer, undated (Box-folder 18: 21)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Posters, undated (Box-folder 18: 22)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Button order request, 1996 (Box-folder 18: 23)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Description of Servas, undated (Box-folder 18: 24)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Publicity handbook, undated (Box-folder 18: 25)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Letterhead, undated (Box-folder 18: 26)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Rose Tischler Peace and Social Justice Memorial Committee, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 18: 27)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Limitations proposal, undated (Box-folder 18: 28)
- United States Servas, Inc. - International conferences, 1998 (Box-folder 18: 29)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Financial records, 1978 (Box-folder 18: 30)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Financial records, 1979 (Box-folder 18: 31-32)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Financial records, 1980 (Box-folder 18: 33-34)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Insurance records, 1982-1999 (Box-folder 19: 1)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Host renewal forms, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 19: 2-3)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Donors, undated (Box-folder 19: 4)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Brochures, 2003 (Box-folder 19: 5-6)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Traveler renewal cards (Box-folder 19: 7-8)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Publications. Transitions Abroad, 2004 (Box-folder 19: 9)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Publications. Servas Compass, 2003 (Box-folder 19: 10)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Bob Liutweiler correspondence and writings, 2003-2007 (Box-folder 19: 11-12)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Host renewal forms, 2006 (Box 20)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Host lists, 2006-2007 (Box-folder 21: 1-2)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Thank you letters, 2006 (Box-folder 21: 3)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Donors and contributors, 2007 (Box-folder 21: 4)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Financial mismanagement. Board recommendations, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 21: 5)
- Note cards, Servas Nepal, undated (Box-folder 21: 6)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Miscellany, 2007 (Box-folder 21: 7)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Miscellaneous correspondence regarding Board meetings, retreats, and committees, 2007-2008 (Box 22)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Expenses and balance books, 1995-1998 (Box 23)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Invoices and tax records, 1999 (Box 23)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Expenses, 1998-1999 (Box 24)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Expenses, 1998 (Box 25)
- Bob Liutweiler file, 1990-2003 (Boxes 26-28)
  Includes subject files and research materials relating to sustainable gardening and different educational programs Liutweiler was involved with, including the Social and Technical Environmentally Appropriate Development Institute (STEADI).
- Meeting minutes, 1987-2006 (Box-folder 28: 6)
- Miscellany, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 28: 7)
- Notes, 2003 (Box-folder 28: 8)
- Newsletters, 2007 (Box-folder 28: 9)
- Miscellany, 2005-2007 (Box-folder 29: 1)
- Conferences, 1998-2004 (Box-folder 29: 2)
- Newsletters, 2005 (Box-folder 29: 3)
- Publicity, 2005 (Box-folder 29: 4)
- Board of Directors file, 2006 (Box-folder 29: 5)
- Correspondence (Box-folder 29: 6)
- Compact disc - Servas News, 2006 (Box-folder 29: 7)
- Board of Directors file, 1987 (Box-folder 29: 8)
- Photographs, undated (Box-folder 29: 9)
- Tree planting program, 2001 (Box-folder 29: 10)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Partners for Democratic Change, 2006 (Box-folder 29: 11)
- Servas - Interviewers, 2002 (Box-folder 29: 12)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Financial records, circa 2004 (Box-folder 29: 13-14)
- United States Servas, Inc. - G. Michael Payne, circa 2004 (Box-folder 30: 1)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Travel, 2001-2006 (Box-folder 30: 2)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Administrative cont'd., undated (Box-folder 30: 3)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Camp counselors, undated (Box-folder 30: 4)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Judy, undated (Box-folder 30: 5)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Host list supplement, 2006 (Box-folder 30: 6)
- United States Servas, Inc. - Photographs, 1950 (Box-folder 30: 7)
- Servas International - United Nations, circa 1970 (Box-folder 30: 8)
- U.S. Servas key persons list, 1998 (Box-folder 31: 1)
- Administrative oversight, 2002 (Box-folder 31: 2)
- Global Fund for Women, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 31: 3)
- Administrative, 1992-2003 (Box-folder 31: 4)
- Individual files, 1920-1993 (Box-folder 31: 5)
- Servas International, 1987-2002 (Boxes 32-34)
- Scrapbooks, 1990-1997 (Boxes 35-36)
- VHS, compact cassette, CDs, undated (Box 37)
- Stamps, circa 1990 (Box-folder 38: 1)
- Bob Liutweiler file, circa 1949 (Box-folder 38: 2-3)
- Memorabilia, undated (Box-folder 38: 4)
- Postcards, circa 1997 (Box-folder 38: 5)
- Brochures, 1990-2001 (Box-folder 38: 6)
- Photographs, 1970-2001 (Box-folder 38: 7-8)
- Conference materials, 1998-2004 (Box 39)
- Servas International, 1976-2004 (Box-folder 40: 1-3)
- Writing course, circa 1990 (Box-folder 40: 4)
- Cut-outs, undated (Box-folder 40: 5)
- Servas International - Bob Liutweiler file, 2008 (Box-folder 41: 1-3)
- Servas International - Notebooks (Box-folder 41: 4)
- Servas International - Africa, 1985 (Box-folder 41: 5)
- Servas travel program, 2004 (Box-folder 41: 6)
- Servas International - Handbook, 1998 (Box-folder 41: 7)
- Servas International - Minutes, 1966-1981 (Box-folder 42: 1)
- Servas future, circa 1980 (Box-folder 42: 2)
- Servas International - Communication, circa 1980 (Box-folder 42: 3)
- Servas outreach, 1990 (Box-folder 42: 4)
- Servas International - Bylaws, 1980 (Box-folder 42: 5)
- Servas International - Individual files, 1987-1995 (Box-folder 42: 6)
- Servas International - Host and traveler survey, 1992 (Box-folder 42: 7)
- Patrice Samara - Executive Director, 2005 (Box-folder 43: 1)
- Style guide, undated (Box-folder 43: 2)
- Correspondence, 1948-1950 (Box-folder 43: 3)
- Servas history, undated (Box-folder 43: 4)
- Bioville, circa 1996 (Box-folder 44: 1)
- Other peace organizations and social activism, 2008 (Box-folder 44: 2-4)
- Other peace organizations and social activism, 2008 (Box-folder 45: 1)
- Bob's stories, undated (Box-folder 45: 2)
- Slides, 1978-1987 (Box-folder 45: 3)
- Host list handbooks, 1989-1998 (Boxes 46-47)
- Financial records (tax exemption and tax return information), 1985-1998 (Boxes 48-49)
- Financial Committee minutes, 1995-2002 (Box 50)
- Host list handbooks, 1989-1998 (Boxes 51-52)
- Servas headquarters, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 53: 1-3)
  Scope and Content
  Includes information regarding the lease at 11 John Street.
- Student travelers, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 53: 4)
- Host list handbooks, 1992-2007 (Box 54)
- Host list handbooks, 2004-2007 (Box 55)
- Administrator's manual, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 55: 1)
- Host list handbooks, 2004-2007 (Box 56)
- Travelers file, 2002
  Interviewer's checklists that were submitted with the travelers' applications.
  - 2002 Travelers T (Box-folder 56: 1)
  - 2002 Travelers U/V (Box-folder 56: 2)
  - 2002 Travelers W (Box-folder 56: 3)
  - 2002 Travelers XYZ (Box-folder 56: 4)
  - 2002 Travelers N/O (Box-folder 57: 1)
  - 2002 Travelers P/Q (Box-folder 57: 2)
  - 2002 Travelers R (Box-folder 57: 3)
  - 2002 Travelers SA - SL (Box-folder 57: 4)
  - 2002 Travelers SM - SZ (Box-folder 57: 5)
  - 2002 Travelers I/J (Box-folder 58: 1)
  - 2002 Travelers K (Box-folder 58: 2)
  - 2002 Travelers L (Box-folder 58: 3)
  - 2002 Travelers M (Box-folder 58: 4)
  - 2002 Travelers Mc (Box-folder 58: 5)
  - 2002 Travelers D (Box-folder 59: 1)
  - 2002 Travelers E (Box-folder 59: 2)
  - 2002 Travelers F (Box-folder 59: 3)
  - 2002 Travelers G (Box-folder 59: 4)
  - 2002 Travelers H (Box-folder 59: 5)
  - 2002 Travelers A (Box-folder 60: 1)
  - 2002 Travelers B (Box-folder 60: 2-3)
  - 2002 Travelers C (Box-folder 60: 4)
- Floppy disks, CD-Rs, zip discs, undated (Box 61)